Guide to the Swimming and Diving Team Records, 1932-[ongoing] UA.13.02.0014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Swimming and Diving Team records
1932-[ongoing]
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Sports Information Office
UA.13.02.0014
5.6 Linear Feet
5500 Items
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Swimming and Diving Team Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the SI Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the swimming and diving team at Duke University. The material ranges in date from 1932-ongoing.
Related Material
Athletic Dept. Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Scrapbooks.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photographic Negative Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Chanticleer Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletic Council Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletics Reference Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Clippings (information artifacts); Duke University. Sports Information Office; Duke University -- Sports; Duke University -- Swimming and Diving -- History -- 20th century; Duke University. Sports Information Office
- General Yearly Files, 1932-1990; 1994-1996; 1999-2000 1932-2000, 4 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  The General Yearly Files contain information about both the women's and men's swimming and diving teams, although the bulk of the records in this series concern the men's swimming and diving teams.
  - 1932-1967 (Box 1)
  - 1967-1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981-1990 (Box 3)
  - 1994-1996, 1999-2001 (Box 4)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving, 1975-1999, 2 boxes
    - 1975-1990 (Box 5)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 6)
  - Men's Swimming and Diving, 1990-1999, 1 boxes
    - 1990-1999 (Box 7)
- Media Guides, 1970-ongoing, 1 boxes
  - 1970-1981; 1987-2008 (Box 8)
  - various dates, c.2 (Box 8)